[{"id": 753, "question": "Do you like chocolate? Maybe most people do. A box of it can be a great gift. Buy one for a friend and give it as a surprise. See how happy that person gets. Say you just got a box of chocolate. Which piece do you pick first? A man has studied people's choices. He says they tell something about the person. Did you choose a round piece? You are a person who likes to party. Did you choose an oval shape? You are a person who likes to make things. Picking a square shape shows something else. The person is honest and truthful. You can depend on him or her. What kind of chocolate do you pick? Maybe you like milk chocolate. This shows you have warm feelings about the past. Dark chocolate means something else. A person who chooses it looks toward the future. What about white chocolate? Would you c...\n\nQ: Picking a round shape of chocolate shows that a person   _  .", "options": ["likes singing, dancing and drinking", "likes to do something for others", "is good at making things", "can be depended on"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 479, "question": "Friends play an important role in our lives, and although we can't be more familiar with the fact of friendship, we often don't clearly understand how we make friends, especially with Americans. Here are some pieces of advice on making friends with Americans: 1. Visiting places Americans enjoy: parties, churches, restaurants, parks and sports clubs. 2. Be willing to take the first step. Don't wait for them to get close to you. Americans in China may not know you speak English. They may be uncomfortable if they can't speak your language. 3. Use small talks to open the conversation. Ask them where they're from, why they come to China, etc. . Remember: Be careful not to ask personal questions about age, salary and so on. 4. Show an interest in their culture, their country or their job. Americ...\n\nQ: What is mainly discussed in the text?", "options": ["It's very important to be a good friend of an American.", "Some advice on how to make friends with Americans.", "Something about the friendship in America.", "Friendship is the most important in our life."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 844, "question": "If you are looking for the place that has everything, there is only one place to visit, and that's New York. It's a whole world in a city. The World of Theater: All of New York is a stage. And it begins with Broadway. Where else can you find so many hit shows in one place? Only in New York! The World of Music: Spend an evening with Beethoven at Lincoln Center. Swing to the great jazz of Greenwich Village. Or rock yourself silly at the hottest dance spots found anywhere. The World of Art: From Rembrandt to Picasso. From Egyptian tombs to Indian teepees. Whatever kind of art you like, you will find it in New York. The World of Fine Dining: Whether it's roast Beijing duck in Chinatown, lasagna in little Italy, or the finest French coq au vin found everywhere, there is world of great taste wai...\n\nQ: From the text we know that \"Rembrandt\" is most likely to be the name of a famous  _  .", "options": ["actor", "musician", "cook", "painter"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1308, "question": "To a large degree, the measure of our peace of mind is determined by how much we are able to live in the present moment. Regardless of what happened yesterday or last year, and what may or may not happen tomorrow, the present moment is where you are -- always! We allow past problems and future concerns to control our present moments, so much that we end up anxious, frustrated, depressed, and hopeless. We often convince ourselves future will be better than today. John Lennon once said, \"Life is what's happening while we're busy making other plans. \"When we're busy making other plans\", our children are busy growing up, the people we love are moving away and dying, our bodies are getting out of shape, and our dreams are slipping away. In short, we miss out on life. Many people live as if life...\n\nQ: Why are some people depressed and anxious day and night?", "options": ["Because they fear they cannot pass their tests.", "Because past problems and future concerns control their present moment.", "Because the people they love want to leave them alone.", "Because they make some mistakes in the past."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 737, "question": "How to protect children Web fans from unsuitable material on-line while encouraging them to use the Internet has long been discussed in the US. For some parents, the Internet can seem like a jungle, filled with danger for their children. But jungles contain wonders as well as danger. With good guides, some education, and a few precautions( ), the wilds of the Internet can be safely navigated. \"Kids have to be on-line. If we tell our kids they can't be allowed to surf the Internet, we're cutting them off from their future,\" said an expert. Most kids have started to use search engines. Many of them are great for finding tons of interesting Internet sites, and they can also locate places where you might not want your kids to go. There are search engines designed just for kids. A certain softw...\n\nQ: What is the best way to protect children from improper material?", "options": ["To talk to the children and persuade them to tell right from wrong.", "To be nearby when the children are surfing the Internet.", "To fix a content screener on the computer.", "To buy some search engines for children."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 179, "question": "School education is very important and useful. Yet no one can learn everything from school. A teacher, no matter how much he knows, he can not teach his students everything they want to know. The teacher's job is to show his students how to learn. He teaches them how to read and how to think. So much more is to be learned outside school by the students themselves. It is always more important to know how to study by oneself than to learn some facts or a formula by heart. It is actually quite easy to learn a certain fact in history or a formula in mathematics. But it is very difficult to use a formula in working out a maths problem. Great scientist, such as Einstein, Newton and Galileo, didn't get everything from school. But they were all so successful and invented so many things for men. Th...\n\nQ: If a student want to learn better, the most important thing for him to do is  _  .", "options": ["to learn all the useful facts and formula by heart", "to do everything as his teacher have said in class", "to absorb as much knowledge from his teacher as possible", "to think more while he is studying"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2812, "question": "Trees are useful to man in three very important ways: they provide him with wood and other products, they give him shade, and they help to prevent drought and floods. Unfortunately, in many parts of the world man has not realized that the third of these services is the most important. In his eagerness to draw quick profit from the trees, he has cut them down in large numbers, only to find that without them he has lost the best friends he had. Two thousand years ago a rich and powerful country cut down its trees to build warships, with which to gain itself an empire. It gained the empire but, without its trees, its soil became hard and poor. When the empire fell to pieces, the country found itself faced by floods and starvation. Even though a government realizes the importance of a plentifu...\n\nQ: The purpose that the writer wrote this article is to    _   .", "options": ["tell people the use of wood", "tell people the function of tree roots", "warn that man mustn't destroy forests any more", "explain how trees help to prevent drought and floods"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2731, "question": "The intelligence times provide us much convenience,but at the same time,some of our abilities are being weakened gradually. 1. Memorizing phone numbers It was annoying to remember numbers. Now we simply add them to our contacts list. That usually works well unless our device is lost,stolen,or damaged. No one can be expected to remember all their contact numbers. What we can do is memorize 5 of our most important contact numbers. This should include a mixture of family,friends and business. If you're really ambitious you can memorize 5 contacts for each category. 2. Map-reading skills The convenience and effectiveness of GPS guidance systems and digital maps generated by search engines is unquestionable. They've definitely made our lives easier. What we don't get from using these devices an...\n\nQ: What's the disadvantage by adding all numbers to the contacts list?", "options": ["We may only have the ability to remember 5 numbers.", "It's hard to find the number from the contacts list.", "We might lose all our phone numbers accidentally.", "Our device is more easily damaged or stolen."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1019, "question": "A group of graduates, well established in their careers, were talking at a reunion and decided to visit their old university professor, now retired. During their visit, the conversation turned to complaints about stress in their work and lives. Offering his guests hot chocolate, the professor went into the kitchen and returned with a large pot of hot chocolate and other things including cups-porcelain , glass, crystal, some plain looking, some expensive, some elegant -- telling them to help themselves to the hot chocolate. When they all had a cup of hot chocolate in hand, the professor said: \"I notice that all the nice looking and expensive cups were taken, leaving behind the plain and cheap ones. While it is normal for you to want only the best for yourselves, that is the source of your p...\n\nQ: What caused the professor to say those words?", "options": ["Their graduation.", "Their reunion.", "Their visit.", "Their complaints."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1191, "question": "Certain plants and animals can survive under what seem like impossible conditions. Blind fish live freely under ocean depths that are ly dark and cold. Bacteria live at temperatures of 600 degF or a higher in places where the heat comes from the deep earth. One of the most remarkable achievements that we can observe directly is the ability of the plants and animals in the desert. In the Death Valley ,temperatures of 134 degF in the shade have been officially reported Yet lizards live there ,along with 600 species of plants, 30 species of mammals? and even fish. While the days are terribly hot, the nights are extremely cold. Temperatures can fall down by as much as 50 degF. Plants called xerophytes are perfectly adapted to the extremely dry conditions. These plants have survived by developi...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best express the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["The Death Valley is a living museum ,where many plants and animals exist.", "Plants and animals can survive in the desert by adjusting to the environment.", "Days in desert can be deadly hot, while nights can be terribly cold.", "Bacteria survive in the ocean depth and the desert burning heat."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2826, "question": "Are you the kind of person who likes staying in unusual places? If the answer is \"yes\", then try the world's coldest hotel in Jukkasjarvi in the north of Sweden. But go in winter to all you'll find is a pool of water, because the hotel melts every spring! The man who runs the Artic Hall Hotel is Nils Yngve Bergqvist. He built his first ice building for an art exhibition in 1991 and he designed the present hotel-over 200 meters square-himself. It took workmen about two months to pile 1,000 tons of snow onto a wooden base. As the weather got colder, the snow froze and then they removed the base. The whole building and everything in it are made of snow-except for the wooden front door. There's a theatre which Nils uses for a jazz club, a radio station and a large ice bar. As you can imagine, ...\n\nQ: Which of the following about the Artic Hall Hotel is NOT true?", "options": ["It is the coldest hotel in the world.", "You can go to the hotel in spring.", "The hotel is in the north of Sweden.", "Nils Yngve Bergqvist is the owner of the hotel."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3022, "question": "For years we have been dieting strictly after the year-end overeating, afraid that when summer. comes, the bigger size we have accumulated will betray how we ate. Now scientists say, it's a little bug that causes obesity . As the holiday season with its abundant feasting arrives, millions of food lovers are keeping an eye on their figures. But scientists have found that weight gain is not about too much Christmas turkey or hot chocolates, but some bacteria in your guts . Chinese scientists recently discovered a type ofbacteria in guts that may be to blame for obesity. A research team led by Zhao Liping, a professor in Shanghai, has identified a precise link between a particular kind ofbacteria and unusual weight gain. \"The endotoxin released by the bacterium can activate a gene that helps ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["Scientists didn't try to find out the cause of overweight.", "There is a link between mice's overweight and human's.", "Lita proved the link between bacteria and weight gain.", "Scientists found bacteria may be related to many diseases."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3080, "question": "C.O.P.D blocks air flow through the lungs. It makes breathing difficult. The leading cause of C.O.P.D. is cigarette smoking. Experts at the National Institutes of Health in the United States say there is no cure to the damage to the lungs. Dawn Demeo is an assistant professor at Harvard Medical School in Boston, Massachusetts. She said, \"By 2020, C.O.P.D. may be the third leading cause of death across the world.\" C.O.P.D. is a new name for emphysema and chronic bronchitis . These are the two most common forms of the disease. Many people with C.O.P.D. have both of them. And Doctor Demeo says more women than men now die from the disease. She is the lead author of a study by a team from Harvard's Brigham and Women's Hospital and the University of Bergen in Norway. The new study adds to findin...\n\nQ: It can be known from the study that  _  .", "options": ["female smokers die faster than male ones.", "women are more likely to suffer from the damaging effects of smoking than men.", "O.P.D than women.", "in the group of people under the age of 60, men suffered more from"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 413, "question": "Grown-ups are often surprised by how well they remember something they learned as children but have never practiced ever since. A man who has not had a chance to go swimming for years can still swim as well as ever when he gets back in the water. He can get on a bicycle after many years and still ride away. He can play catch and hit a ball as well as his son. A mother who has not thought about the words for years can teach her daughter the poem that begins \"Twinkle, twinkle, little star\" or remember the story of Cinderella or Goldilocks and the Three Bears. One explanation is the law of overlearning, which can be stated as follows: Once we have learned something, additional learning trials increase the length of time we will remember it. In childhood we usually continue to practice such sk...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of Paragraph 1", "options": ["Children have a better memory than grown-ups.", "People remember well what they learned in childhood.", "Poem reading is a good way to learn words.\"", "Stories for children are easy to remember"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 998, "question": "It'll be an ordinary morning,like all the others.But instead of being woken up by the buzzing of an alarm clock, you'll be roused by the smell of freshly made coffee,light entering your room as the curtains open automatically,and a gentle back massage provided by your high-tech bed. This is what a typical person's life will be like two decades from now,according to The Guardian. Want to know more? After you get up,your apartment will be like an electronic orchestra with you as the conductor.With simple moves of your hand and spoken instructions,you'll be able to control your apartment's temperature,humidity,music and lighting.You'll be able to look through the day's news on translucent screens while your breakfast waits for you in the automatic oven. As you move into your kitchen,maybe you...\n\nQ: According to the text,in two decades,", "options": ["you'll be able to rely on an electronic orchestra to wake you up instead of an alarm clock", "a tiny microchip in your phone will treat you when you are sick", "you will be able to adjust the conditions of your apartment via oral instructions or simple hand gestures", "technology will be smart enough to help us with important things like preparing for a presentation"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 115, "question": "Any high school students lucky enough to be accepted to Harvard University can easily count themselves among the country's best and brightest. The story of David Boone's journey from sleeping on a park bench to one of Harvard's dorm rooms, certainly stands out from the crowd of his peers. David, a 17-year-old senior at a MC2 Stem, a high school in Cleveland, Ohio that focuses largely on engineering and science classes with the help of a grant from the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, was offered a full-ride scholarship to Harvard in the fall. His family life has been complicated for the past few years after gangs and economic hardships resulted in him being separated from his family and forced to look after himself on the streets and park benches in Cleveland. Because both his grandmothe...\n\nQ: How does David feel now when he thought of his life of being homeless?", "options": ["Grateful.", "Painful.", "Shameful.", "Doubtful."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2233, "question": "A new international study shows that some people's biological clock plays a powerful role for their life expectancy, regardless of lifestyle choices. Published in the latest issue ofAgingon Wednesday, the study has found the most definitive evidence to explain why some people keep healthy lifestyle but die younger than others. Geneticist Steve Horvath from the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), led a team of 65 scientists around the world to record age-related changes to human DNA, analyse blood samples collected from 13, 000 people and estimate their lifespan. A higher biological age, regardless of actual age, consistently predicts an earlier death, the study says. \"You get people who are vegan, sleep 10 hours a day, have a low-stress job, and still end up dying young,\" Horvath...\n\nQ: Some people keep healthy lifestyle but die younger than others because   _  .", "options": ["their biological clock is not powerful enough", "the most definitive evidence has been found", "they have a higher actual age than others", "they ages at a relatively faster biological rate"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2780, "question": "Hunan Satellite TV is losing its leading position? There's reason for saying this. In 2012, the reality talent show , the voice of China, on the Zhejiang Television became the most popular program in China. The reaon for its popularity was really because its excellent quality? Or can we assume that without any opponent, we can't tell a contestant is winning because he is really talented or because there's no comparison? The administrative department really contributed a lot in the popularity of the voice of China. In the past, there was no other draft shows ranked as high as Super GirlandSuper Boy. Even though there were some draft shows which seemed to share the popularity, it never turned out ture. All the other draft shows were shodowed by the ones on Hunan TV. One example was that sinc...\n\nQ: What's the author's attitude towards the voice of China?", "options": ["supportive", "optimistic", "hopeful", "doubtful"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1474, "question": "If you're a man and you're reading this, congratulations: you're a survivor. According to statistics, you're more than twice as likely to die of skin cancer than a woman, and nine times more likely to die of AIDS. Even if you make it to the end of your natural term, about 78 years for men in Australia, you'll die on average five years before a woman. There're many reasons for this--typically, men take more risks than women and are more likely to drink and smoke--but perhaps more importantly, men don't go to the doctor. \"Men aren't seeing doctors as often as they should,\" says Dr. Gullotta. \"This is particularly so for the over-40s, when chances of diseases are higher .\" Gullotta says a healthy man should visit the doctor every year or two. For those over 45, it should be at least once a ye...\n\nQ: Why does the author congratulate his men readers at the beginning of the passage?", "options": ["They are more likely to survive serious diseases today.", "Their average life span has been greatly prolonged.", "They have lived long enough to read this article.", "They are sure to enjoy a longer and happier life."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1341, "question": "Once a general manager wanted to test his people, who had come from all over India, about their values of life. He announced that in their folders , there is PVC pouch and in it there is a seed. When they return, they must put the seed in a pot with good soil and look after it very well. He would hold a competition at the next year's seminar and the best plants would be awarded suitably. Everyone did what was told to him. A year passed quickly. And the next year in a big hall, what a great scene! There were hundreds of pots and a great variety of plants-all except one. In this pot was soil, but no plant! The owner of the pot was standing quietly and feeling ashamed of himself. The general manager called him on the stage. He asked him what happened and he told him the truth. He planted the ...\n\nQ: Why was everyone shocked after they heard the general manager's declaration?", "options": ["They didn't understand why the man failed to get the plant.", "They didn't understand why the man was the winner.", "They didn't know why the manager gave him the best seed.", "They didn't know why they couldn't get the plants."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2384, "question": "International Schools Services Experience teaching overseas Have you thought of working overseas? International Schools Services is looking for teachers for thousands of positions.Schools are looking for experienced, well-trained persons who must meet two of the three criteria: *A four-year bachelor's degree *Certification in a subject *Two years' successful teaching experience in a public or private school Attend one of our International Recruitment Conferences .Hundreds of schools will be available.Over 2,000 positions are expected to be filled. *Atlanta--December 4,201 1--December 6, 2011 *Bangkok--January 4, 2012~January 7, 2012 *Boston--February 5, 2012~February 9, 2012 *San Francisco--February 13, 2012~February 16, 2012 Becoming an international educator will offer you a journey you ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT related to the basic requirements for a teaching position?", "options": ["Travelling experience.", "A four-year bachelor's degree.", "Certification in a subject.", "Certain teaching experience."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2883, "question": "On the way home from school, Jack always passes a park. His mother said it was dangerous to pass by the park at night, but it is the fastest way home. Today, after finishing soccer practice, Jack was walking toward the park as usual. Suddenly, Jack heard someone calling him, \"Excuse me!\" Jack turned around, and there was an old woman. \"Yes, ma'am.\" Jack answered politely. \"Don't pass by the park tonight.\" Her voice was weak and dry. \"Okay, ma'am,\" said Jack carelessly. The old woman held Jack's hand strongly, and said, \"I mean it!\" Jack felt the hairs on his neck stand up. As soon as the lady let go of his hand, he started to run. This time, he ran so fast that he didn't have time to think where he was going. When he stopped, he realized he was in the middle of the park. He remembered what...\n\nQ: Why did Jack run home like an arrow?", "options": ["He was terribly frightened.", "He was late for a thriller.", "He was racing with the old lady.", "He was ordered to do so."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3313, "question": "There has been much discussion recently about reducing the weight of English in China's high-stake tests such as the national college entrance examination. It is argued by some applauding the recent change to reduce the importance of English in tests so that it will lead students to focus more on learning Chinese. The TV program Writing in Chinese has exposed the problem that students and the general public cannot write in Chinese as they used to do. Some blame the design of the curriculum for giving English an equal or greater amount of emphasis, which might have contributed to the failure in teaching Chinese. But this is probably not a fair accusation since children in English speaking countries cannot spell either. I doubt that studying English in itself hurts the study of Chinese. In f...\n\nQ: In the writer's opinion, what should be done to solve the argument?", "options": ["Increasing time spent in learning Chinese.", "Increasing time spent in learning English.", "Reducing the weight of English in examinations.", "Improving the learning outcomes effectively."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2173, "question": "Summer school is something a kid will never forget.For some, it's a way to advance past their classmates.For most, summer school is' a requirement in order to graduate with their classmates I can remember being forced into taking a summer school course.It was not the school that forced me into this awkward situation it was my mother. I was a 16-year-old kid in a new school; My school did not offer summer courses so I had to take my course at an alternative school in the city.It was an experience I will never forget.I was not concerned with making friends.I was there to get credit for a course that I should have received credit for the previous semester.It was.my doing that landed me in the situation and it was important that I understood this. The fees were lowest but the experience was am...\n\nQ: What made the author go to summer school for the first time?", "options": ["What he had done.", "His mother's wish.", "His own requirement.", "Study competition."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2114, "question": "The landmark success of herbal expert Tu Youyou, the first Chinese woman national to win a Nobel prize in science, hasaroused an extreme sense of national pride and hopes on the future of traditional Chinese medicine (TCM). Tu, born in 1930, shared the 2015 Nobel Prize for Physiology or Medicine with Irish-born William Campbell and Japan's Satoshi Omura for her discoveries concerning a therapy against malaria. She discovered Artemisinin , a drug that has significantly reduced thedeath rates for patients suffering from malaria . \"Artemisinin is a gift for the world people from the traditional Chinese medicine. It is of great importance for curing malaria and other infectious diseases and for protecting the health of the world people,\" Tu said in Beijing. \"The discovery of Artemisinin is a s...\n\nQ: Which of the following is Not True?  _", "options": ["Tu's winning the prize hasaroused a strong feeling of nation pride in China.", "Premier Li Keqiang praised medical researchers for their work and achievements.", "The congratulatory letter shows that both China's strengths and international standing have reached the highest rank around the world.", "The Lasker Award is awarded to people for their excellent contributions to medical science every year."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1430, "question": "Money spent on advertising is money spent as well as any I know of.It serves directly to assist a rapid distribution of goods at reasonable prices, thereby establishing a firm home market and so making it possible to provide for export at competitive prices.By drawing attention to new ideas it helps enormously to raise standards of living.By helping to increase demand it ensures an increased need for labour, and is therefore an effective way to fight unemployment.It lowers the costs of many services: without advertisements your daily newspaper would cost four times as much, the price of your television license would need to be doubled, and travel by bus or tube would cost 20 per cent more. And perhaps most important of all, advertising provides a guarantee of reasonable value in the produc...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["Advertising and promotion.", "Informative function of advertising.", "Advantages and disadvantages of advertising.", "Benefits of advertising and its characteristics."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1049, "question": "Cyberspace, the connections between computers in different places, considered as a real place where information, messages and pictures exist, mirrors the real world in many ways. People ask for information, play games, and share hobbies. Others buy and sell products. Still others look for friendship, or even love. Unlike the real world, however, your knowledge about a person is limited to words on a computer screen. Identity and appearance mean very little in cyberspace. Rather, a person's thoughts--or at least the thoughts they type--are what really count. So even the shyest person can become a chat room star. Usually, this \"faceless\" communication doesn't create problems. Identity doesn't really matter when you're in a chat room discussing politics or hobbies. In fact, this emphasis(,) o...\n\nQ: By saying \"With so many unknowns, it's easy to let one's imagination 'fill in the blanks'\", the writer means that   _  .", "options": ["the Internet allows people to get more information about their loved ones", "the Internet makes it easy for people to imagine how others view them", "people usually get to know each other by chance through the Internet", "people may be disappointed when they meet in person"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1061, "question": "In recent years many countries of the world have been faced with the problem of how to make their workers more productive. Some experts claim the answer is to make jobs more varied. But do more various jobs lead to greater productivity? There is evidence to suggest that while variety certainly makes the worker's life more enjoyable, it does not actually make him work harder. As far as increasing productivity is concerned, then variety is not an important factor. Other experts feel that giving the worker freedom to do his job in his own way is important, and there is no doubt that this is true. The problem is that this kind of freedom cannot easily be given in the modern factory with its complicated machinery which must be used in a fixed way. Thus while freedom of choice may be important, ...\n\nQ: For a worker on an assembly line in a car factory, the job is not enjoyable because   _  .", "options": ["he can only make a part of a car", "he does not know what he is doing", "his life in spare time is more interesting", "the importance of his job is not clear to him"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1602, "question": "Taiwanese fishing boats that sailed to the Diaoyu Islands to protest Japan's \"purchase\" of part of the islands completed their voyage Tuesday morning and have set sail for home. Local media reported that the boats finished their protest at 9:15 a.m. and are expected to return to a port in northeast Taiwan's Yilan county at noon Wednesday. Although the boats originally numbered 75,they were joined at sea by other boats from different parts of Taiwan, raising the total number to about 100 vessels. Organizers said the voyage was made to protect Taiwanese fishing rights in nearby waters and to protest Japan's \"purchase\" of part of the Diaoyu Islands. The Japanese government announced a plan to \"purchase\" part of the islands earlier this month despite repeated protests from the Chinese governme...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of this passage?", "options": ["Japan declared to purchase China's Diaoyu Islands.", "Japan's purchase of Diaoyu Islands aroused nationwide protest.", "The Diaoyu Islands belong to China!", "China plays an important part in Japan's economy development."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3320, "question": "With five breakout games, Jeremy Lin has become the NBA's newest star. In the New York Knicks' 92-85 won over the Los Angles Lakers last Saturday, Lin had a career-high 38 points.A day later, he led the Knicks to their fifth victory, 100-98 to Minnesota Timberwolves.In his previous games, Lin, 23, had 23 points against the Washington, 25 points against New Jersey and 28 against Utah in his first start. Lin is smart.Before graduating from high school in California, he had sent his application to all the Ivy League Schools .He only got into Harvard and Brown, and he chose Harvard.In 2010, Lin graduated with a degree in economics. Lin is the first Chinese-American player in the NBA.He was born in the US and his family is Asian.Although not born in China, Lin has attracted nearly all Yao Ming'...\n\nQ: From the passage, it can be inferred that    _   .", "options": ["Lin is the team leader of the Knicks", "the Knicks' success only depends on Lin", "the Knicks'coach puts strong hopes on Lin", "the Knicks is sure to win the season this year"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3050, "question": "Schoolgirls have been wearing such short skirts at Paget High School in Branston that they've been ordered to wear trousers instead. All skirts will be banned from September. Tight-fitting trousers will also be forbidden and Muslim head-dresses will have to be \"school blue'' color. Head teacher Don Smith said, \"One of the big problems for us at the school has been the number of girls who have been wearing inappropriately short skirts. This has been an area of particular concern at a time when there has been a lot of material nationally about the sexualisation of young people.\" He also said, \" It will be impractical to police the length of girls' skirts. A blanket ban will be easier for staff to put into practice. We did not want to arrive at a situation where we were telling girls their sk...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the passage?", "options": ["New School Rules Set", "Girls' Skirts Forbidden", "Traditional Neckties Gone", "Different Opinions Voiced"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 835, "question": "Homesick is a compound word made up of HOME and SICK.You know what each word means on its own, of course.But think about what the words mean when they are used together.Homesick means SICK FOR HOME. Now think for a minute about SEASICK.If you change the word home in the definition to the word sea, would the definition fit SEASICK? Seasick means SICK BY THE MOVEMENT ON THE SEA. When you are homesick ,the only place you want to be is at home.When you are seasick, the last place you want to be is at seA. Have you ever heard of a person being heartsick? Heartsick doesn't mean that something is wrong with a person's heart.people are heartsick when they are hurt deep inside and when they feel as if their hearts are broken. But, on the other hand, we have such compound words as handshake, handsta...\n\nQ: The definitions of handshake, handstand and handbag are  _  .", "options": ["easy to know", "difficult to know", "impossible to learn", "unnecessary to learn"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3097, "question": "The U.S. Department of Labor statistics show that there is an oversupply of college trained workers and that this oversupply is increasing. Already there have been more than enough teachers, engineers, physicists, aerospace experts, and other specialists. Yet colleges and graduate schools continue every year to turn out highly trained people to compete for jobs that aren't there. The result is that graduates cannot enter the professions for which they were trained and must take temporary jobs which do not require a college degree. On the other hand, there is a great need for skilled workers of all sorts: carpenters, electricians, mechanics, plumbers, TV repairmen. These people have more work than they can deal with, and their annual incomes are often higher than those of college graduates....\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that the author believes that   _  .", "options": ["every young man and woman should go to college", "college education is a bad thing", "people with a college education should receive higher pay", "fewer people should go to college while more should be trained for skilled jobs"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1279, "question": "In 1974, after filling out fifty applications, going through four interviews, and winning one offer, I took what I could get ----- a teaching job at what I considered a distant wild area: western New Jersey. My characteristic optimism was alive only when I reminded myself that I would be doing what I had wanted to do since I was fourteen ------- teaching English. School started, but I felt more and more as if I were in a foreign country. Was this rural area really New Jersey? My students took a week off when hunting season began. I was told they were also frequently absent in late October to help their fathers make hay on the farms. I was a young woman from New York City, who thought that \"Make hay while the sun shines\" just meant to have a good time. But, still, I was teaching English. I ...\n\nQ: The students behaved badly in the writer's classes because", "options": ["They were eager to embarrass her.", "They didn't regard her as a good teacher.", "She didn't really understand them.", "She didn't have a good command of English."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2427, "question": "Learning a Second Language Some people learn a second language easily. Other people have trouble learning a new language. How can you help yourself learn a new language, such as English? There are several ways to make learning English a little easier and more interesting. The first step is to feel confident about learning English. If you believe that you can learn, you will learn. Be patient. You don't have to understand everything all at once. It is natural to make mistakes when you learn something new. We can learn from our mistakes. The second step is to practise your English. For example,write in a diary every day. You will get used to writing in English,and you will feel comfortable expressing your ideas in English. After several weeks, you will see that your writing is improving. Bes...\n\nQ: What is not helpful for you to enjoy learning English?", "options": ["To communicate in English.", "To worry about making mistakes.", "To think about what you did after each class.", "To make a record of the achievements."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1914, "question": "When we look at the sky and see a bright light moving quickly across it or coming towards the earth, we talk about seeing a \"shooting star\" or a \"falling star\". These moving lights are not, in fact, stars at all. They are small pieces of matter from outer space, which burn up as they enter the Earth's atmosphere. The correct name of them is meteoroids. Any pieces that make it to the Earth's surface without completely burning up are known as meteorites. A meteor is actually the name given to the light we see when a meteoroid is burning up. When a meteorite hits the Earth at speeds between 11 and 72 kilometers a second, it can do amazing damage. A very large meteorite could knock the earth out of its orbit. If this happened, all life on Earth would probably become extinct . The path we follo...\n\nQ: Meteors are   _  .", "options": ["small planets", "the same as asteroids", "from broken parts of asteroids", "the light we see when meteoroids hit our atmosphere"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1586, "question": "I was on vacation, and in my mind, vacation does not mean setting my hotel room alarm clock for 6 am. But when you're in Aruba and hoping to reserve a beachside palapa , that's exactly what you do. Tourists begin lining up at the crack of dawn to secure these umbrella-like wood structures that are covered with dried and woven palm leaves. They then place towels on chairs and call them theirs for the day, whether they remain there or not. I knew nothing of _ on my first day in Aruba. I saw an empty chair covered with a towel and took it. It was a big mistake. For many visitors, a week bathing in the sun is the only activity they wish to pursue. It sounded good to my girlfriend, Barbara, and me after Boston's awful winter. Six more inches of snow was predicted on the day we left. The sun, th...\n\nQ: Tourists get up at 6 am because they   _  .", "options": ["want to see the sunrise early", "need to check out early", "want to have fun longer", "need to reserve a beachside palapa"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2043, "question": "I arrived at the bus station much too early for the London bus, which was not to leave until five to twelve. I pushed through the crowds, looking for somewhere to sit down. Scores of people were standing about, or struggling along with their bags and the cases to find the right lines. There was a party of school girls. I could see teachers trying to keep them in order. But there was nowhere for me to sit. I stepped into the station buffet. I looked up at the clock there. It was only twenty to twelve. I found a seat opposite a large mirror on the wall. Just then a friend of mine called Jim came in and sat with me. \"What time is your bus?\" asked Jim. \"Oh, there's a plenty of time yet,\" I answered. \"Oh, I'll get some drinks then,\" said Jim. We talked while drinking. Then I looked at the clock...\n\nQ: Jim came to the station buffet at about   _  .", "options": ["twenty to twelve", "twenty past twelve", "half past one", "twenty past eleven"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 606, "question": "No matter where he lives, 16-year-old Danny Lopez feels like an outsider: he is half-Mexican and half-white. At his private high school in wealthy northern San Diego, California, US, Lopez is too brown to fit in, whereas for the Mexican side of his family in National City, just a dozen miles from the border, he is too white to belong. Different from both sides, Lopez is silent in school. He focuses on his passion for baseball and working hard to improve the pitches that have kept him off the school team. Mexican Whiteboy, by Matt de la Pena, is about a teenager's search for identity. It was named as one of the Top Ten Best Books for Young Adults in 2009 by the US Young Adult Library Services Association. When Lopez's mother decides to go to live with her wealthy white boyfriend in San Fran...\n\nQ: When Lopez found it is hard for him to fit in, he   _  .", "options": ["starts writing a book about himself", "begins to look for identity with the help of Mexican Whiteboy", "loses his interest in baseball", "works in the fields in which he was kept off the school team"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 648, "question": "I was dirty smelly hungry and some somewhere beneath all that, suntanned .It was the end of an Inter-Rail holiday.My body couldn't take any more punishment. My mind couldn't deal with any more foreign timetables, currencies or languages. \" _ ,\" I said, as I stepped onto home ground.I said exactly the same thing the following year.And the next, all I had to do was buy one train ticket and, because I was under twenty--five years old,I could spend a whole month going anywhere I wanted in Europe. Ordinary beds are never the same once you've learnt to sleep, in the passage of a train, the rhythm rocking you into a deep sleep. Carrying all your possessions on your back in a tucksack makes you have a vefy basic approach to travel,and encourages incredible wastefulness that can lead to burning soc...\n\nQ: Why did the writer originally buy an Inter--Rail ticket?", "options": ["To get to one place cheaply.", "To meet other young people.", "To see a lot of famous places", "To go on a tour of Europe."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2999, "question": "With my hands and knees on the floor of the airplane, I was searching for an old lady's missing hearing aid during the flight from Sydney to Los Angeles. It occurred to me that this may not be the most dignified posture for a Buddhist nun . I had seen the old lady from the seat in front of me as she walked up and down the passage with a flashlight. I asked a few times what was wrong, but she didn't answer at first --- she couldn't hear me. She was wearing a woolen coat. Judging from her accent, she came from Eastern Europe. Do you know what hearing aids cost? Thousands, especially for the new tiny hidden-in-the-ear type she described. It takes a long time for an appointment to make a new one, and many doctor visits to get the thing adjusted right. Therefore, my dignity seemed less importan...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To tell us a story about kind help.", "To warn us to be more careful.", "To teach us how to find the lost thing.", "To present the love from all people on board."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1617, "question": "Dear residents of Molten, We can't keep silent in the current wild situation when prices for all existing products are skyrocketing unbelievably. The enormous figures on price tags for food products have caused a real panic. We've perfectly realized that, and that's why we have kept bread prices affordable for all this time. At the moment all our reserves are exhausted. Stocks of bread-baking ingredients such as flour, sugar, butter and the like are running out. To buy what we need at reasonable prices is virtually impossible today. However, we all need bread every day, which means we will be forced to buy everything we need at much higher prices. The cost of bread closely depends on ingredients. Another financial crisis has led to a 300-percent increase of prices for butter, vegetable oil...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["bread may end up as an article that many people can no longer afford", "the local people have responded positively to recent SOS messages from Figaro", "bread may become less tasty in recent months", "the government has a tradition of helping out local businesses in difficult times"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2078, "question": "The United States government has decided that food from cloned cattle, pigs and goats is safe to eat. The Food and Drug Administration also says it found no risks in meat and milk from cloned animals. The F.D.A. looked at studies for several years before it announced its decision in a final report this month. The United States Department of Agriculture supported the findings. But it says time is needed to clear the way for marketing meat and milk from clones. The F.D.A. will not require any product to be registered as coming from clones. A producer would need to label a product \"clone-free\". The agency says that could be misunderstood because the food is not different from other food. But activists argue that the F.D.A. based its decision on incomplete research into possible risks. The Cen...\n\nQ: Why are products from cloning not widely used for feeding?", "options": ["Because cloning attempts often fail.", "Because they are not safe to eat.", "Because cloning is cruel.", "Because they are expensive."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2600, "question": "Chinese President Hu Jintao, on his way to talks with President George W. Bush in prefix = st1 /Washington, on Tuesday met with Bill Gates. After the meeting with Gates, the world's richest man, at Microsoft's headquarters, Hu restated that China would move against software pirates all the time. At Microsoft Corp.'s campus, Hu said on Tuesday he admired what Microsoft Chairman Bill Gates had achieved. He also sought to reassure Gates that China is serious about protecting intellectual property rights . \"Because you, Mr. Bill Gates, are a friend of China, I'm a friend of Microsoft,\" Hu said. \"Also, I am dealing with the operating system produced by Microsoft every day,\" he added, to laughter. Gates responded: \"Thank you, it's a fantastic relationship,\" and then said: \"And if you ever need a...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Hu Visits Microsoft.", "Protecting Intellectual Property Rights.", "Bill Gate's, A Friend of China.", "Americans Welcome President Hu."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1558, "question": "\"Thanks for coming,\" Everett said, shaking hands with Mr. Hanson, the town councilor . \"I'm curious about the ideas in your letter.\" Mr. Hanson nodded toward the parking lot near where they stood. \"Please tell me more.\" Everett took a deep breath. \"Ever since the school closed two years ago, this area has become worse. But if we clean up the litter and repair the fence, it will be a great place for a skateboard park.\" Mr. Hanson scanned the broken concrete, nodding. \"The old school is being adapted to a community arts centre. This area could become a vital part of the neighbourhood again.\" \"Here's a picture of a skateboard park in another town. Look how busy it is.\" Everett was relieved that the community representative seemed receptive to the idea. Mr. Hanson studied the photograph, and t...\n\nQ: Where were Everett and Mr. Hanson talking?", "options": ["In the city hall.", "Outside a park.", "Near the parking lot.", "In the art centre."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 692, "question": "Woody Guthrie left California for New York in 1940. There he met Alan Lomax, an expert on America's traditional music. He collected and recorded traditional American folk music, which had few fans at that time. When he heard Woody sing, Lomax knew he had found a true singer of American folk music. Lomax recorded many of Woody's songs for the Library of Congress. Three years later, Woody published a book called Bound for Glory. It was about his early life and travels. From this book people came to learn how Woody had spent his unhappy youth. His mother, Nora Guthrie, died of Huntington's Disease in 1929 when he was only seventeen years old. There was no treatment for the disease. About twenty years later, the disease also began to attack the son. Woody's health got worse and worse, and fina...\n\nQ: Which of the following could be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["America's own music", "A fighter for social justice", "This land is your land", "A folk music hero"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1099, "question": "Hilton English Language Center Information for New Students CLASS TIME: 8:30a.m.--10:00a.m., 10:30a.m.--12:00a.m., 1:30p.m.--3:00p.m.. The Language Center is open Monday to Friday. Each class has one afternoon free per week. On the first day, go to the lecture hall to check your timetable. SELF-ACCESS: The language laboratory (Room 1110) is open Monday to Friday from 3:15p.m. to 5:00p.m. for all full-time students. You can learn how to use computers for language games or word-processing . There are tapes for students to borrow to practice their English. Go in and ask the teacher to show you. If you plan to take public examinations, there are dictation and listening comprehension tapes for you to practice with. There are cloze exercises on the computers. Ask your class teacher for a list of...\n\nQ: When do classes begin and end on a full day?", "options": ["8:30a.m.--1:30p.m..", "8:30a.m.--3:00p.m..", "8:30a.m.--3:15p.m..", "3:15p.m.--5:00p.m.."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2305, "question": "Engineers should embrace the arts, Sir John O'Reilly, a fellow of the Institution of Engineering and Technology, argued in a lecture. About 59% of engineering companies in the IET's 2014 survey feared skill shortages could threaten business. \"There is nothing as creative as engineering,\" Sir John told the reporter. He says science, technology, engineering and mathematics - often known as \"Stem\" subjects, are vital for a modern knowledge economy. But there is a massive shortfall in the number of recruits - with a recent study by the Royal Academy of Engineering saying the UK needs to increase by as much as 50% the number of Stem graduates it produces. Delivering this year's Mountbatten Lecture at the Royal Institution, Sir John argued that engineers should recognise the role of the arts in ...\n\nQ: According to a recent study by the Royal Academy   _   .", "options": ["skill shortages could threaten business", "engineering graduates are not as creative as expected", "there are not enough arts graduates produced in the UK.", "the UK needs more graduates in science, technology, engineering and mathematics"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1211, "question": "For almost two months Dominic York, a 23-year-old hairdresser, wandered about hospitals all night, wearing a white coat and pretending he was a doctor. Yesterday he proudly claimed in court that despite his complete lack of medical experience or qualifications, he had saved several people's lives. He had even been allowed to assist a surgeon during an emergency operation on a patient who was about to die on something she had swallowed. \"I watched one of those TV dramas about a hospital and suddenly I felt like playing one of the roles myself. So I put on a white jacket and a stethoscope and walked around one of the biggest hospital in London. At first I just watched. Once you learn how doctors talk to patients, nurses and others doctors, it's easy to take people in,\" he said. One of the pa...\n\nQ: Why was Laura Kennan in hospital?", "options": ["She had swallowed something and almost died.", "She had to have and emergency operation.", "She had been injured in a road accident.", "She had lost consciousness while driving."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1004, "question": "No matter where you travel in Asia, you'll find yourself faced with a new culture. You can start your Asian exploration by visiting some of these attractive cities first. Beijing, China Beijing is the second largest city in China and serves as the capital. The city is so old, in fact, that almost every building has some sort of cultural or historic features -- no matter how small. Getting around the city you'll find yourself faced with amazing temples , the largest palaces in the world, and many works of art that leave you breathless. Siem Reap, Cambodia Siem Reap is the capital city of Siem Reap Province in northwestern Cambodia. Siem Reap has a lot of French and Chinese-style architectures. In the city, there are traditional dance performances, silk farms, fishing villages and a bird san...\n\nQ: If you want to visit the biggest place where ancient emperors lived in the world, you can go to   _  .", "options": ["Beijing", "Siem Reap", "Kathmandu", "Kyoto"], "answer": 0}]